<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<languages>
    <language name="English" id="en">
        <PageTypeTreeFilter>
            <GlobalSettings>
                <AllowUserSettingsDescription>Enables users to override the global available page type settings defining their own set in the PageTypeTreeFilter tab of their user settings.</AllowUserSettingsDescription>
                <AllowUserSettingsLabel>Allow users to override the global available page types settings</AllowUserSettingsLabel>
                <Heading>Global PageTypeTreeFilter Settings</Heading>
                <ResetDescription>Resets the values to the default ones; all page types are allowed and users may override at their discresion.</ResetDescription>
                <ResetLabel>Reset to default</ResetLabel>
                <ResetSuccessfulMessage>The settings were successfully reset to their default values. Please refresh web browser (F5) to see them in effect.</ResetSuccessfulMessage>
                <SaveDescription>Click to save your global PageTypeTreeFilter settings.</SaveDescription>
                <SaveLabel>Save</SaveLabel>
                <SaveSuccessfulMessage>Your changes were saved successfully. Please refresh web browser (F5) to see them in effect.</SaveSuccessfulMessage>
            </GlobalSettings>
            <PageExplorerAdapter>
                <FilterSelectorLabel>Filter on Page Type:</FilterSelectorLabel>
                <SettingsLinkText>Settings</SettingsLinkText>
                <SettingsLinkTooltip>Global settings for the PageTypeTreeFilter functionality. Only available to web administrators.</SettingsLinkTooltip>
            </PageExplorerAdapter>
            <PageTypeSelector>
                <ShowAllText>--- Show all pages ---</ShowAllText>
            </PageTypeSelector>
            <Units>
                <PageTypePicker>
                    <AddPageTypeToolTip>Add page type</AddPageTypeToolTip>
                    <AvailableDescription>These are all of the page types in the system.</AvailableDescription>
                    <AvailableLabel>Available page types</AvailableLabel>
                    <Description>Please select the page types that you wish to make available in the edit mode PageTypeTreeFilter functionality.</Description>
                    <RemovePageTypeToolTip>Remove page type</RemovePageTypeToolTip>
                    <SelectedDescription>These are the page types that you have selected to be shown in the PageTypeTreeFilter drop down list in edit mode.</SelectedDescription>
                    <SelectedLabel>Selected page types</SelectedLabel>
                </PageTypePicker>
            </Units>
            <UserSettings>
                <EnablePersonalSelectionDescription>Check to enable your own personal selection of page types for the PageTypeTreeFilter functionality drop down list.</EnablePersonalSelectionDescription>
                <EnablePersonalSelectionLabel>Use personal selection</EnablePersonalSelectionLabel>
                <GuiPlugIn>
                    <description>User specific PageTypeTreeFilter settings</description>
                    <displayname>PageTypeTreeFilter</displayname>
                </GuiPlugIn>
                <UserSettingsDisabledMessage>User specific page type selection has been disabled globally. If this is a problem for you, please ask your web administrator to enable the settings, or change the available page types globally.</UserSettingsDisabledMessage>
            </UserSettings>
        </PageTypeTreeFilter>
    </language>

    <language name="svenska" id="sv">
        <PageTypeTreeFilter>
            <GlobalSettings>
                <AllowUserSettingsDescription>Tillåt användare att själva bestämma vilka sidtyper som de ska kunna filtrera på i PageTypeTreeFilter-fliken i de användarspecifika inställningarna.</AllowUserSettingsDescription>
                <AllowUserSettingsLabel>Tillåt användarspecifika inställningar för tillgängliga sidtyper</AllowUserSettingsLabel>
                <Heading>Globala PageTypeTreeFilter-inställningar</Heading>
                <ResetDescription>Återställer standardvärdena; alla sidtyper går att filtrera på, och användare får göra egna inställningar om de vill.</ResetDescription>
                <ResetLabel>Återställ standardvärden</ResetLabel>
                <ResetSuccessfulMessage>Inställningarna har återställts till sina standardvärden. Vänligen uppdatera sidan i din webbläsare (F5) för att kunna använda dem.</ResetSuccessfulMessage>
                <SaveDescription>Klicka för att spara dina globala PageTypeTreeFilter-inställningar.</SaveDescription>
                <SaveLabel>Spara</SaveLabel>
                <SaveSuccessfulMessage>Dina inställningar har sparats. Vänligen uppdatera sidan i din webbläsare (F5) för att kunna använda dem.</SaveSuccessfulMessage>
            </GlobalSettings>
            <PageExplorerAdapter>
                <FilterSelectorLabel>Filtrera på sidtyp:</FilterSelectorLabel>
                <SettingsLinkText>Inställningar</SettingsLinkText>
                <SettingsLinkTooltip>Globala inställningar för sidträdets sidtypsfiltrering. Denna länk visas endast för användare som har administratorbehörighet.</SettingsLinkTooltip>
            </PageExplorerAdapter>
            <PageTypeSelector>
                <ShowAllText>--- Visa alla sidor ---</ShowAllText>
            </PageTypeSelector>
            <Units>
                <PageTypePicker>
                    <AddPageTypeToolTip>Lägg till sidtyp</AddPageTypeToolTip>
                    <AvailableDescription>Detta är alla sidtyper som finns i systemet.</AvailableDescription>
                    <AvailableLabel>Tillgängliga sidtyper</AvailableLabel>
                    <Description>Vänligen välj de sidtyper som du önskar göra tillgängliga för filtrering i EPiServers sidträd.</Description>
                    <RemovePageTypeToolTip>Ta bort sidtyp</RemovePageTypeToolTip>
                    <SelectedDescription>Detta är de sidtyper som användaren kommer att kunna filtrera på i EPiServers sidträd.</SelectedDescription>
                    <SelectedLabel>Valda sidtyper</SelectedLabel>
                </PageTypePicker>
            </Units>
            <UserSettings>
                <EnablePersonalSelectionDescription>Markera för att använda dina egna inställningar för vilka sidtyper som ska vara tillgängliga, istället för de globalt valda.</EnablePersonalSelectionDescription>
                <EnablePersonalSelectionLabel>Använd egenvalda sidtyper</EnablePersonalSelectionLabel>
                <GuiPlugIn>
                    <description>Användarspecifika inställningar för sidträdsfiltreringen.</description>
                    <displayname>PageTypeTreeFilter</displayname>
                </GuiPlugIn>
                <UserSettingsDisabledMessage>Användarspecifika inställningar har avaktiverats globalt. Om detta är ett problem för dig, vänligen be din webbadministratör att tillåta detta, eller byta de tillgängliga sidtyperna globalt.</UserSettingsDisabledMessage>
            </UserSettings>
        </PageTypeTreeFilter>
    </language> 
</languages>
